So here's my solution for creating an array of features,
下面说说我是如何创建 features 数组的
reviews that have either been padded on the left with zeros
我们要么在左侧填充 0 要么截取到特定长度
until their sequence length on or truncated at that length.
使影评长度达到标准长度
First, I'm actually creating an array of zeros,
首先创建一个 zeros 数组
that's just the final shape that I know I want.
表示最终想要的形状
That is, it should have as many rows as I have reviews in
行数应该与 reviews_ints 输入数据中的影评数一样
the input reviews_ints data into as many columns as the specified sequence length,
列数应该与指定的序列长度一样
and this will just hold all the zero integers for now.
暂时存储的整数都为 0
Then for each review in my list,
对于列表中的每条影评
I'll put it as a row in my features array.
我都将其当做行放入 features 数组中
The first review is going to go on the first row,
第一条影评放在第一行
and the second in the second, and so on.
第二条放在第二行 等等
I started out thinking of my short review case.
下面处理短影评
I want to keep a left padding of zeros,
我需要在左侧填充 0
up until I reach where that review can fill the remaining values.
直到整个长度达到标准长度
So, I'm looking at filling my features,
为了填充 features
starting at the index that's at the end of the features row,
从 features 行的结束索引位置开始
minus the length of the input review.
减去输入影评的长度
So, if a reviewer show,
如果影评很短
this means our features are going to keep the zeros which are padding on the left,
features 将保留左侧填充的 0
and the review tokens will be on the right side.
影评标记将位于右侧
It turns out that I only have to add one more piece to
对于很长的影评
this line to make this work for a long reviews too.
只需添加这一小部分就搞定了
Hear for annual review including those longer than the given sequence length,
对于任何影评（包括长于标准长度的超长影评）
I'm truncating them at that sequence length,
我都在指定序列长度那截断
and this should fill the corresponding features row.
并填充到相应的 features 行中
So, this loop will do this for every review in reviews_ints,
这个循环将遍历 reviews_ints 中的每条影评
and then returns these features.
然后返回这些 features
Below I'm running my test code.
在下面运行测试代码
Here I'm creating features passing in my list of
创建一个 features
reviews_ints and a sequence length equal to 200.
传入 reviews_ints 列表并将序列长度设为 200
I don't trigger any of these error messages,
结果没有触发这些错误消息
so I know my dimensions are correct,
所以维度设置正确
and then printing out the first ten values of the first three rows here.
在这里输出前三行的前十个值
And here's what these rows look like.
看起来是这样的
A lot of these start with zeros,
有很多行以 0 开头
which is what I expect for left padding,
表示左填充
and others have filled up these rows with various token values.
其他位置填充了各种标记值
So, this is great. And I'll also add that.
很棒还要提一点
In this step, we've actually introduced a new token into our review features.
在这一步 我们向影评特征中引入了新的标记
Remember that before, all words in our vocabulary hadn't associated integer value,
之前词汇表中的所有字词都没有关联整数值
and we started organizing with the value one.
我们开始用 1 标记化字词
So, in our vocab_to_int dictionary,
vocab_to_int 字典
we had integers from one up to 74,000 or so.
包含从 1 到 74,000 左右的整数
And here by adding zero as padding,
我们通过添加 0 来填充影评
I've effectively inserted the zero token into our vocabulary.
向词汇表中插入了 0 标记
Okay. Now for your next and the last data transformation
Ok数据已经处理得差不多了
exercise with our data in nice shape, next,
还有最后一个转换练习
I want you to split the features and encoded labels into three different datasets,
请将特征和编码的标签拆分为 3 个不同的数据集
training, validation, and test sets.
分别代表训练集、验证集和测试集
You'll need to create datasets for grouping our features and
你需要为特征和标签分别创建数据集
labels like train_x and train_y, for example.
例如 train_x 和 train_y
And we'll use these different sets to train and test our model.
我们将使用这些数据集训练和测试模型
So, I've defined a split fraction,
我定义了一个拆分比例 split_frac
split_frac, as the fraction of data to keep in the training set.
请按照该比例将训练集中的数据保留为训练数据
This is set to 0.8 or 80 percent of data.
我将该比例设为 0.8 或 80%
The 20 percent of the data that's left should be split in
剩下的 20% 应该一分为二
half to create the validation and testing data respectively.
分别充当验证集和测试集
So, I'll leave this as an exercise.
请完成这道练习
And next, I'll go over how I split the data and I'll show you
接下来我将演示我是如何拆分数据的
some PyTorch resources we can use to
并介绍一些实用的 PyTorch 资源
effectively batch and iterate through these different datasets.
这些资源能够帮助我们批处理和遍历不同的数据集